Victor Crowley Lives.
Hatchet II is a horror, comedy, thriller film directed by Adam Green.
Picking up right where the original ended, Marybeth escapes the
clutches of the swamp-dwelling killer Victor Crowley.
After learning the truth about her family’s connection to the hatchet-wielding madman, Marybeth returns to the Louisiana swamps along
with an army of hunters to recover the bodies of her family and exact the bloodiest revenge against the bayou butcher.
Marybeth Dunstan, played by Danielle Harris.
Victor Crowley / Thomas Crowley, played by Kane Hodder.
Reverend Zombie, played by Tony Todd.
Justin, played by Parry Shen.
Trent, played by R.A. Mihailoff.
Layton, played by AJ Bowen.
Hatchet II is a 2010 American slasher film written and directed by Adam Green.
It is the sequel to Hatchet and the second
installment in the titular film series.
Picking up right where the first film ended, Hatchet II follows Marybeth as she
escapes the clutches of the deformed, swamp-dwelling killer Victor Crowley.
After learning the truth about her family's connection to the hatchet-wielding madman, Marybeth returns to the Louisiana swamps along
with an army of hunters to recover the bodies of her family and exact the bloodiest revenge against the bayou butcher.
The film sees the return of Kane Hodder and Tony Todd who portrayed Victor
Crowley and Reverend Zombie in the 2006 film, respectively.
Danielle Harris portrays Marybeth, a role originally played by Tamara Feldman.
The film was originally screened at the 2010 London
FrightFest Film Festival on August 26, 2010.
It was released unrated in the United States on October 1, 2010.
A sequel, Hatchet III, was released in 2013.
The film explores themes of voodoo, beheading, spider, swamp, disappearance.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.